Hello.
こんにちは
May I ask your name?
お名前聞いていいですか?
This is Minami.
みなみです
Minami-chan.
み なみちゃん
How old are you now?
今、いくつですか?
I'm 19 years old now.
今、19歳です
You're young.
若いっすね
Minami-chan, do you have a boyfriend now?
みなみちゃん、今、彼氏とかはいるの?
I don't have a boyfriend right now.
今、彼氏いないです
There's no one there.
はいないんだ
How much is missing?
どんくらいないの?
It's been about a year.
1年くらいですかね
About a year?
1年くらい?
Don't you want it?
ほしくないの?
I feel like it's still good for now.
今はまだいいかなって感じです
That's right.
そうなんだ
So when was your first experience?
じゃあ、初体験はいつ?
My first experience was when I was a third year high school student.
初体験は、高校3年生の時です
18 years old?
18歳?
yes.
はい
18 years old?
18歳の?
Well, if you're going to be away for about a year,
じゃあ、1年くらいいないとだったら、
There aren't any anymore.
もう全然いないね
I agree.
そうですね
So, how many people have experience?
じゃあ、経験人数は?
The number of experienced people is 3 people.
経験人数、3人ですね
That's right.
そうなんだ
Isn't there a type?
タイプとかいないの?
I guess your type is a kind person.
タイプ、優しい人とかですかね
That's right.
そうなんだ
So, what kind of phrases do you like?
じゃあ、どういうフレーズが好きなんだ?
I'm a bit of a M, so I'd like to be bullied.
ちょっとMなので、いじめられたいです
Do you like being attacked?
攻められたりするのが好きなんだ?
Your skin is white.
肌白いよね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
So, do you have a favorite place like raw liver?
じゃあ、生肝体とか好きな場所とかある?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Well, maybe over there.
まあ、あそことかですかね
Where is that place?
あそこってどこ?
Something like cleatrice.
クリートリスとか
How do you want your cleatris?
クリートリスはどうやってしたいの?
I want to be touched.
触られたりしたいです
Do you want to be touched?
触られたりしたい?
yes.
はい
What is it?
なんだ
hey.
ね
I agree.
そうですね
Is that okay?
と れてるけど、いい?
yes.
はい
All of Minami's special parts are captured.
みなみちゃんのめっちゃのところ全部とれてるよ
good?
いい?
yes.
はい
So stand there and look behind you.
じゃあ、そこを立てて、後ろを見てみて
Put it on the front?
手前つける?
yes.
はい
Can I have it come with a hat?
帽子付きだしてもらう?
Take off your pants.
パンツ脱いちゃって
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
yes.
はい
You've done it right.
きっちりしてきたね
It's better to do it like this.
こういうしてきた方がいいな
Yes, that's right.
うん、そうですよね
I'm wearing it.
付けちゃってるよ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
This is so embarrassing.
こっちくらいの恥ずかしい
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Do you understand?
分かる?
I understand.
分かるよ
What did it hit?
何に当たった?
Will it go up to your waist?
腰に上がっちゃう?
A little bit now.
今のちょっと
It feels good.
気持ちいいです
I'm sweating.
汗かいちゃって
Just rub it on your butt, do you understand?
ふっとお尻に擦って、分かる?
I understand.
分かります
I like it.
好きです
Try sitting down.
下に座ってみて
Can you touch me more petane?
もっとペタンって触れる?
Ochinchun, about Ochinchun?
おちんちゅん、おちんちゅんぐらい?
What happened?
どうなったの?
It's really hard.
すごい硬い
What kind of dick do you like?
どういうおちんちゅんが好き?
I like hard dicks.
硬いおちんちゅんが好きです
Do you like hard dicks?
硬いおちんちゅんが好き?
Yeah.
うん
Can you take a look at this directly?
これじゃあ、 直接見てくれる?
Want to see it?
見たい?
I want to see it.
見たいです
Do you usually get angry when you get up?
普段って、 上がるところでちゅうちゃいする?
Why not?
しないの?
Do you hesitate when you get up?
上がるところでちゅうちゃいする?
Yeah.
うん
Just comb it out
くしゃ出してみ
hand.
て
I'll try it any time.
いつ もやってみちゃうね
Going up?
上がるって?
Yeah.
うん
Are you dropping something here?
ここでちゅうちゃい落としてるの?
Yeah.
うん
Drop it?
落として?
Yeah.
うん
Drop it?
落として?
Please wait here?
ここ で ちゅうちゃい?
Yeah.
うん
Drop it.
落として
Are you dropping something here?
ここでちゅうちゃい落としてるの?
Then I put my shoes on and dropped it.
そこでくつみで、 落として
Drop it.
落として
Yeah.
うん
everytime
いつも
I like getting used to it.
慣 れるの好きだもん
hey.
ね
I burst into tears.
涙 が出てきちゃって
You don't know.
知らないでしょ
I've been sleeping a lot.
いっぱい寝ちゃってる
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Where are you embarrassed?
どこが恥ずかしいの?
No, it's embarrassing.
いや、恥ずかしい
Tell me the embarrassing place.
恥ずかしい場所教えて
Please take a good look.
うまく見て下さい
I'm bleeding.
血くれちゃった
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Do you like straight lines?
こっち直線の好きなの?
like.
好き
Do you like the bottom part?
下のところが好きなんだっけ?
I like clean.
クリーンが好きです
What should I do to clean?
クリーンどうするの?
I want you to touch me.
触ってほしいです
Do you want me to touch you?
触ってほしい?
Spread your legs yourself.
自分で足を広げて
Please.
お願いして
Open your hands.
手を開いて
Is this so?
こうですか?
Where do you want me to touch you?
どこ触ってほしい?
Clean to the touch.
クリーン触ってください
Please touch.
触ってください
where?
どこ?
I want you to touch it clean.
クリーン触ってほしいです
What sound?
何の音?
embarrassed
恥ずか
Yes.
しい
Ugh, does it just keep ringing?
う ちうち鳴っちゃうだけ鳴ってきちゃうの?
Does it make a ringing noise?
鳴らし音してきちゃうの?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Do you like this one better?
こっちの方が好き?
I like it.
好きです
Just a little bit.
ちょっとだけ
It's really scary.
すっごい怖いですね
Please take a break.
ゆっくり休憩してください